<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>home/</title>
    <link>https://yashlamba.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on home/</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2022 Yash Lamba</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 21:52:20 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yashlamba.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Simulate</title>
      <link>https://yashlamba.github.io/projects/simulate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yashlamba.github.io/projects/simulate/</guid>
      <description>Story of learning flutter through a fun project!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snake Game in Minutes with Flutter</title>
      <link>https://yashlamba.github.io/blogs/flutter-snake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 21:52:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yashlamba.github.io/blogs/flutter-snake/</guid>
      <description>Source: Snake Game
DartPad: Play Snake Game
 Introduction Snake game is probably one of the most known video games in the world and I have built it multiple times, why? Because it’s a good intro project to any new language or framework. I have built it with Python, C++, Javascript, and Dart (Flutter). I frequently use it as an example when I’m teaching someone the basics of a language/framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Flutter on Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL)</title>
      <link>https://yashlamba.github.io/blogs/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 16:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yashlamba.github.io/blogs/1/</guid>
      <description>Most developers prefer to use Linux or MacOS for development and the major reason in simple terms is the terminal and the ease they provide with their development environments. Windows has always been avoided by most developers (as far as I see in the community) but recently, after the announcement of Windows terminal and the increasing popularity of Windows Subsytem for Linux, many people have taken a stab at developing with Windows without having to install a Linux distro or use a Virtual Machine or in extreme cases, buy Macbooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://yashlamba.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yashlamba.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, here&amp;rsquo;s a little about me.
 I am a full-stack developer, currently building/breaking/fixing stuff at HackerRank. I have worked with a lot of technologies and am quite fast in learning new things as well. Currently, I am figuring out backend architecture, design, infra scaling and cloud. I have also tinkered with ML/AI (can get a lot of things working) but am not actively improving myself in those.
I always find myself in situations where I know the most complicated stuff but end up Googling the simplest things (like how to read csv hehe).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handwrite CLI</title>
      <link>https://yashlamba.github.io/projects/handwrite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yashlamba.github.io/projects/handwrite/</guid>
      <description>Trying to solve the handwritten assignment crisis...</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handwrite Web</title>
      <link>https://yashlamba.github.io/projects/handwrite-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yashlamba.github.io/projects/handwrite-web/</guid>
      <description>Fitting Handwrite in a web app.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
