<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on home/</title>
    <link>https://yashlamba.com/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on home/</description>
    <image>
      <title>home/</title>
      <url>https://yashlamba.com/images/social_preview.png</url>
      <link>https://yashlamba.com/images/social_preview.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.149.1</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>2025 Yash Lamba</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 20:51:20 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://yashlamba.com/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Web3 Experience: Polygon Fellowship 2022</title>
      <link>https://yashlamba.com/blogs/polygon-fellowship-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 20:51:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yashlamba.com/blogs/polygon-fellowship-2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-the-fellowship&#34;&gt;About the Fellowship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Polygon Fellowship organised by Devfolio is an exclusive 8-week mentor-led learn-to-earn program to get started with Web3 development. The program has 2 tracks: Beginner Track and Builder Track. As the names suggest, Beginner track is focused on developers who are new to web3/are looking to start there web3 journey. Builder track is for more advanced developers who already know a bit web3 and are looking to work on mentor-guided projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake Game in Minutes with Flutter</title>
      <link>https://yashlamba.com/blogs/flutter-snake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 21:52:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yashlamba.com/blogs/flutter-snake/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snake game is probably one of the most known video games in the world and I have built it multiple times, why? Because it’s a good intro project to any new language or framework. I have built it with Python, C++, Javascript, and Dart (Flutter). I frequently use it as an example when I’m teaching someone the basics of a language/framework.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, we’ll build the Snake Game with Flutter. Some interesting things we’ll cover:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with Flutter on Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL)</title>
      <link>https://yashlamba.com/blogs/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 16:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yashlamba.com/blogs/1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most developers prefer to use Linux or MacOS for development and the major reason in simple terms is the &lt;strong&gt;terminal&lt;/strong&gt; and the ease they provide with their development environments. Windows has always been avoided by most developers (as far as I see in the community) but recently, after the announcement of Windows terminal and the increasing popularity of Windows Subsytem for Linux, many people have taken a stab at developing with Windows without having to install a Linux distro or use a Virtual Machine or in extreme cases, buy Macbooks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
